{
    "subject": "resource/Spanish_West_Indies",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Spanish_colonial_real",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Spanish West Indies is Spanish colonial real.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.914712131023407,
            "question": "What type of real was used as currency in the Spanish West Indies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8314895033836365,
            "question": "Was the currency of the Spanish West Indies unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8189772367477417,
            "question": "What was the currency used in the Spanish West Indies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8137170076370239,
            "question": "Were there any other currencies used alongside the Spanish colonial real?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7794478535652161,
            "question": "How did the end of colonialism affect the currency of the Spanish West Indies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7706361413002014,
            "question": "To which colonial power did the Spanish West Indies belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7640874981880188,
            "question": "What does 'Spanish colonial real' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6721595525741577,
            "question": "Can you provide an example of a historical transaction using the Spanish colonial real?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6252135634422302,
            "question": "How did the value of the Spanish colonial real fluctuate over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4770645797252655,
            "question": "What factors influenced the monetary system in the Spanish West Indies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Spanish West Indies is Spanish colonial real.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8919_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the value of the Spanish colonial real fluctuate over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8919_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide an example of a historical transaction using the Spanish colonial real?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8919_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'Spanish colonial real' refer to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8919_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8919_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support that the Spanish colonial real was indeed a significant form of currency used in the Spanish West Indies, including areas like Jamaica and other colonies. This information aligns with the query stating that the currency of the Spanish West Indies is the Spanish colonial real."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}